NEEL GEMAVAT (1) Featured

I am an Assistant Manager - Software & Systems at Larsen & Toubro Limited with 3.5 years of experience in BI Services such as Power BI & SQL Server Data Tools (SSMS, SSAS, SSIS) currently working as a Business Analyst - Power BI at L&T Corporate IT.



Current Designation: Assistant Manager Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Current Company: Larsen & Toubro Limited Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Location: Mumbai Highest Degree:

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Mumbai Suburbs, Navi Mumbai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Business Intelligence, C#, MS SQL Server, Power BI, LUIS, Dialogflow, MS Azure, SSIS, SSAS, SSMS, Software

Development, Customer Analytics, Digital Analytics, Data Manipulation, SQL, SQL Queries, SQL Server, SQL DBA

Verified: Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

I am an Assistant Manager at Larsen and Toubro Limited with experience working essentially in Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning &

Robotic Process Automation. Additional skills include working on Business Intelligence (BI), Dot Net Framework & Optical Character Recognition. Ability to develop software programs using the abovementioned technologies.

With my deep dive technical experience of more than 3.5 years, I am currently working as the Lead Project Manager for Robotic Process Automation and Artificial Intelligence.

Work Experience

Larsen & Toubro Limited as Assistant Manager Jul 2020 to Till Date

Larsen & Toubro Limited as IT Executive Jul 2018 to Jun 2020

Larsen & Toubro Limited as Graduate Engineer Trainee Jun 2017 to Jun 2018

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science) from KJ. Somaiya College of Engineering, Mumbai in 2017

PG: in 0

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
C#, Microsoft SQL Server		
Power BI		
MDS Services		
Microsoft Azure		
Automation Anywhere		
Work Fusion		

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	
English	Proficient				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time